airfrov.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Airfrov - Get Travellers To Bring Back Overseas Products

Updated: 18 May 2017 

Here at Airfrov, we respect your privacy and protecting it is of utmost importance to us. 

**We collect personal and activity data, only to make your experience better. Not to sell them.**

We utilize customer relationship management technologies to identify you so that we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your profile, time spent on Airfrov and your interactions on Airfrov.

We also collect other personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. With your permission, we may also access other information from services like Facebook connections and friends. By providing us with your information, you consent to the use of your information where necessary for us to perform our services. 

Please feel free to contact us at any time if you ever feel that your safety has been compromised. We will make sure that you are comfortable.

By accepting the Terms of Use you also agree that we are allowed to contact you by email or phone or SMS messaging even if you are on the Do Not Call (DNC) registry.

**Others can see your username and that is all.**

You can check your profile to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. Currently, only your username is visible to other users and we will not disclose other information without your consent. You may contact us by email to deactivate your account from our platform and/or withdraw your consent to the use of your information. Airfrov reserves the right to retain personal data in its documents and records in accordance with the Data Protection Provisions.

**Nobody likes to be hack - we make sure you stay safe.**

We take appropriate steps to secure your personal information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on servers located in any country where we do business.

**When will we disclose your data? Only these.**

Your information may be disclosed to third party organizations partnered with Airfrov for the purpose of fulfilling our services, such as to external logistics companies. We will only disclose your data under certain circumstances as required by the law: (1) with your express consent, (2) to protect our rights or property and other users in a criminal or fraud investigation case or (3) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Subject to time and legal constraint, we will always attempt to notify you prior to releasing any of your data.

**We will keep you updated on our privacy and regulations**

This privacy policy was last updated on 18/05/2017. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.
